JMC Scripts for JAWS - Change Log

Release: 5.1.6
Added an automatic monitoring feature so that important stats like hit points can be checked instantly at any time with a keypress. Press Alt+Control+Insert or Windows+Insert to set the string to match against, such as "HP: ", then press either Alt+Control or Windows from the main JMC window to hear the latest monitor string. This is helpful for action sequences, such as during combat, when it's important to keep track of a specific value repeatedly.
Changed speech output when the JMC window does not have focus, so that the JAWS Cursor will be used instead to prevent confusion with current window speech output.
Fixed a bug where pressing Ctrl+Shift when Hyper Nav Mode is active was not clearing the edit field as expected.
Added speech interrupt refreshes to Quick Nav and Hyper Nav Mode keystrokes plus custom keys, changes are automatic.

Release: 5.1.5
Added the NewTextEvent to catch highlighted text when encountered within the MUD output window to prevent double announcement.

Release: 5.1.4
Added the ability to add the line "use jmc.jsb" to the Default JAWS Script file, so that incoming MUD messages will continue to be announced even when focus is not within the JMC application.
Fixed the virtual buffer refresh issue when using the HyperNav NumPad5 so that pressing review commands such as Ctrl+Shift+Downarrow or Alt+Shift+Downarrow will announce the correct information after this HyperNav key command is executed.
Fixed an issue where pressing different keyboard combinations of Ctrl+Shift were not always clearing the current line as expected so that it should not matter which right or left key is used for this purpose.
Fixed an issue where pressing Up or Down when the Virtual Buffer was active was not reading the previous and next lines as expected when HyperNav Mode was active.
Updated the common.scr.txt file within the root JMC folder so that the SayString function is invoked directly.

Release: 5.1.3
Added the ability to use NumPad5 hotkey when HyperNav mode is active where a custom string can be specified. Pressing Insert+Control will activate HyperNav mode for using the NumPad as compass point navigation hotkeys. Pressing Insert will cancel HyperNav mode. This functionality is different from QuickNav mode which is toggled by pressing Control+Insert+NumPad5, where the WindowsKey is held down while pressing any of the NumPad number keys to perform the same actions.
To set a custom string for HyperNav NumPad5, press Alt+Control+`.
When Control+Insert is pressed to activate HyperNav Mode, QuickNav Mode will also be turned on automatically if this is not already enabled.
A few bug fixes were also made regarding hotkeys that no longer referenced valid scripts.

Release: 5.1.2
Fixed a bug where non string values were being inadvertently announced by JAWS as "0" after being passed to the parseString function from JMC.

Release: 5.1.1
Fixed a bug when updating the jmc.ini JAWS script settings file, where removing a saved host would not remove the saved port key value as expected.
Fixed a menubar bug where pressing Escape after the menubar is opened using Alt does not close the menubar as expected.
Updated the auto update dialog text, and added functionality to review the Change Log after an update has been loaded.

Release: 5.1
Added auto-update functionality for the JMC JAWS scripts using the jFetch script module.

Release: 5
Initial release of the new JMC scripts for JAWS.